Guide to the Goldie Krantz Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Appendix
  - "Atomic Power and Automation." The Marxist Quarterly 3., (1956
  - Barnes, Leonard. Soviet Light on the Colonies. London., 1944
  - Bevan, Aneurin ("Celticus"). Why Not Trust The Tories?, London., 1944
  - Brown, Harrison, and James Real. Community of Fear. Santa Barbara, California., 1960
  - Chapman, Abraham. The North Atlantic Pact: For Peace or War? New York., 1949
  - Clegg, Arthur. New China, New World. London., 1949
  - Commentary 40., (1965 December
  - The Constitution and By-Laws of the Communist Party of the United States of America. New York., 1938
  - Crosby, Alexander L. The Rape of the First Amendment. New York., 1961
  - Dimitroff, Georgi. After Munich. New York., 1939
  - Dissent 8., (1961 Autumn
  - Friends Committee on Legislation. Questions and Answers about Nuclear Tests. San Francisco., 1957
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth. How Keynes Came to America. Stamford, Connecticut., 1965
  - Gorky, Maxim. "On Which Side are You, 'Masters of Culture'?" New Times 16., (1949
  - "The Great Challenge...Feeding the Hungry Millions." Encore., (1962
  - Hutchins, Robert M. The Bill of Rights: Yesterday, Today, Tomorrow. New York., 1956
  - Kahn, Albert E., ed. McCarthy on Trial. New York., 1954
  - Kartun, Derek. Tito's Plot Against Europe: The Story of the Rajk Conspiracy. London., 1949
  - Keyserling, Leon, H. Progress or Poverty: The U.S. at the Crossroads. Washington, D.C., 1964
  - Lehmann, John ed. The Penguin New Writing. Vol. I. New York., 1940
  - Light, Robert E., and Carl Marzani. Cuba versus CIA. New York., 1961
  - McHenry, Beth, and Frederick N. Myers. Home is the Sailor: The Story of an American Seaman. New York., 1948
  - Marion, George. The Communist Trial: An American Crossroads. New York., 1949
  - Marx, Karl. Value, Price and Profit. New York., 1935
  - Masses & Mainstream 2., (1949 November
  - Monthly Review 10., (1958 July-August
  - Morris, George. Where is the CIO Going? New York., 1949
  - Moulton, Harold G., and Louis Marlio. The Control of Germany and Japan. Washington, D.C., 1944
  - Nearing, Scott. Cuba and Latin America: Eyewitness Report on the Continental Congress for Solidarity with Cuba. Social Science Pamphlet No. 5. Harborside, Maine., 1963
  - Sayers, Michael, and Albert E. Kahn. The Great Conspiracy. New York., 1946
  - Smith, Edwin S. Organized Labor in the Soviet Union. New York., 1944
  - Spivak, John L. The "Save the Country" Racket. New York., 1948
  - Stalin, J. On Organization. Little Stalin Library, No. 6. London., 1942
  - Standard, William L. Merchant Seamen and the Law. New York., 1945
  - Tank, Herb. Communists on the Waterfront. New York., 1946
  - Weiss, Max. What Price Profits? New York., 1947